Dear Yeon-jin, whom I miss.
TO YEON-JIN
Do you remember
that I used to hate the summer?
Thankfully, I moved away
before it got even hotter.
I've been organizing my pictures
since yesterday,
but it's taking a while
because they're all such lovely faces.
WEATHERCASTER PARK YEON-JIN
I started picturing in my head
that someday
you might open that front door
and walk in here.
What is all this?
That's Jae-jun and Sa-ra.
These are all pictures of us.
Hey,
who are you anyway?
It's me, Yeon-jin. It's me.
You really haven't changed at all.
You're still so rude.
You should take your shoes off
when entering someone else's home.
You've given me
yet another reason to kill you.
You should have at least recognized me.
Kill me?
You think you can kill me?
Yeah, I will.
I'm going to try my hardest to kill you.
So come quickly, Yeon-jin.
I'm already here.
Oh!
Do you want to hear about
how I came to be where I am now
while you're on your way here?
CHIEF SHIN YEONG-JUN
An official report was filed,
so the guardians have to come
and follow the procedure.
I'll let her off easy, so don't worry.
Yeah. I'll call you.
SUMMER OF 2004
Park Yeon-jin.
-Yeah?
-Why would you bully a friend?
Don't come back for something like this.
Your mother's nearly here, so go.
She's not my friend.
By the way, Mister.
What's going on between you and my mom?
We're friends from middle school.
Oh, so you're like Son Myeong-o to my mom?
That's why you helped her
with her divorce.
And gathered all the evidence
of my dad having an affair.
I thought you slept
with my mom or something.
Let's go now!
The deliveries are backed up.
Get up and go!
You're so embarrassing.
I told you not to come!
It's all good if they make up
and give each other a hug.
Sa-ra, come on.
How can I help you?
I'm Dong-eun's guardian,
her homeroom teacher.
Hey. You came here
with your fucking uniform on?!
And you called the police
over a little prank between friends?
The vice principal got the call--
I'll deal with you later.
Get up, and let's go!
Sir, take me too.
I'm an orphan for a week.
My parents are abroad.
-Golfing.
-Oh yeah?
Then you should have called me.
I'll take him too.
Oh, sure.
Hey, I was wondering
why you are still here.
So, what about your meals?
-I have a housekeeper.
-Oh, do you?
I told you today was important.
You've disappointed me so much today.
I didn't know I'd end up with the cops.
That's why I'm disappointed.
You couldn't handle a girl
who has nothing.
And didn't I tell you
to only hang out with Jae-jun?
And Sa-ra, if you're bored.
The shaman told you
to avoid people with O's in their names
because they'd bring you bad luck.
I'm talking about
Son Myeong-o and Choi Hye-jeong!
Come inside. We're late.
MOON DONG-EUN
Here comes Dong-eun!
It's the same Dong-eun
you get to see every day!
Welcome, Dong-eun.
I'm sorry for bullying you
for all this time.
I wanted to apologize.
You won't be mad anymore, right?
There was no need to call the cops
about it. You scared us.
Speaking of which, Dong-eun,
can you check, from now on,
if the curling iron is hot enough?
Let go! Let me go!
This is a crime! Let me go!
Hey, it's just a small favor.
How is that a crime?
She said she's sorry.
I just want you to check
if it's hot or not.
Is it that hot?
I think it's ready.
Let's see.
Somebody help! Please, somebody help me!
Hey, don't waste your energy!
You can scream all you want,
but nobody will find out.
Nobody's coming for you.
The gym teacher gave us the key!
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm so sick of hearing that.
Why do you guys always ask that?
'Cause even if I do this,
nothing will happen to me,
and nothing will change for you.
Look at you now.
You caused a fucking scene at the station,
but you're right back here.
Has anything changed?
What I'm saying is,
nobody will protect you, Dong-eun.
Not the police, not the school,
and not even your parents.
What do you call a person like that?
An underdog.
You live at an inn, right?
I learned about motel living
thanks to you.
Her rent is due
every full moon, apparently.
That sounds like a total fairy tale!
Wow, Dong-eun must be my fairy godmother.
She even checks the heat
so I can do my hair, right?
Let go!
Let me go!
-Let me go!
-Shut up!
-Let go.
-Myeong-o, shut her up.
Let go!
You're being too loud in a public place.
Hydrogen peroxide solution?
If you give it to me, I'll do it.
There's something on my shirt.
What's on your shirt?
Is it blood?
Please just give me the hydrogen peroxide.
What happened? Who did this?
Did you tell your homeroom teacher?
I've seen a scar like this before.
If it's too hard for you alone,
I'll go with you when you tell him.
Who was it?
Yeah, Mom.
I'll call you back.
It was me.
It was me last time too.
Do you know, Yeon-jin…
that your daughter likes
to look at the world upside down?
Is it because when the world
is upside down,
people will understand you even if
you can't tell some colors apart?
Your shoes look just like my mom's.
So it's you.
Park Yeon-jin's daughter, Ha Ye-sol.
Do you know my mom?
I think about her every day.
Some hatred resembles longing.
It's impossible to get rid of.
"Hatred"?
I don't know that word. What does it mean?
What does hatred mean?
That's so freaking funny!
Huh? What?
Are you gonna run?
Her eyes that turned darker
when she got excited.
What took you so long?
I missed you so much.
Her lips that curled up when she smiled.
Every single strand of her beautiful hair.
Put all of that together,
and that's what hatred is.
She took her shoes off before coming in!
We're real pieces of shit. Shame on us.
Hey, move.
Is this yours?
I found this in the rice container.
-I couldn't believe my own eyes.
-Give that back--
Oh no.
Is Dong-eun mad?
Nice catch.
It's quite a lot!
Really? That's freaking sad.
Dong-eun.
You're so frugal!
Crazy bitch.
What the fuck did you take this time?
Cold syrup or glue?
Stop! Stop doing that!
Dong-eun is so freaking rich!
-It's about 200,000 won.
-Are you paying for all this?
You guys are rich!
You don't need that money!
I'm begging you.
Please give it back, Yeon-jin.
I see you're behaving politely now.
Fine.
I'll give it back.
But I want you to dance
while we're drinking.
Then I won't touch this money. How's that?
-What?
-I said, dance!
Singing and dancing go well
with drinking, you know.
What? You don't want to?
If you really don't want to,
there is another way.
I found this at your place.
You're such a mess right now.
But if you try to act all proud,
then you will become an even bigger mess.
So dance.
In humiliation.
If you don't want to, fine.
But seeing you today, Dong-eun…
even your legs are pretty.
I'll choose the song.
I have so many freaking ringtones.
NURSE'S OFFICE
TEMPORARILY CLOSED
DUE TO RESIGNATION OF THE SCHOOL NURSE
Really? When?
I'll call you later.
Hey, Dong-eun dropped out of school.
But she wrote all of our names
on the withdrawal form.
She gave it to the vice principal,
who is nagging at our teacher right now.
Was it the gym teacher?
In the order of who hit her the most?
Or alphabetical order?
I wonder where my name is on the list.
Can't you read the room?
Hey!
Jae-jun! Yeon-jin!
Come here.
You crazy bitch!
If you want to drop out,
do it without a fuss.
Did you do nothing wrong?
Not a single thing?
If it's come to this,
there's something wrong with you too!
Come redo your withdrawal form now!
SCHOOL WITHDRAWAL LETTER
If this goes to the principal,
it will affect
your work evaluation, Mr. Kim.
I know that, okay? So please.
What is this?
What kind of reason is this?
School violence.
Yeon-jin, Sa-ra, Jae-jun, Hye-jeong,
and Myeong-o are the perps.
And you are a bystander.
Shut that mouth of yours!
Did they break your arm or your leg?
You're walking around
with all your limbs intact.
How is it violence?
How am I a bystander?
You're insane at this point,
you know that?
It's okay for friends
to give each other a slap!
And why
is it okay to slap a friend?
What?
You bragged that your son got
into a university of education, right?
So, is it okay if your son gets slapped
by his friends too--
I've been treating you nicely.
And now you're asking for it.
Wow.
What did you
say about
my son?
Say that again. What did you say?
-Get up!
-Don't do this.
Hey.
-Move. What did you say?
-Mr. Kim!
-Get up! What did you say?
-Kim!
Stop it, now.
Move. Hey!
-Mr. Kim!
-Get out of the way!
-Stop!
-Hey!
-Enough!
-Get up!
NEW WORLD BARBERSHOP
Ms. Jeong, your phone's ringing.
Coming!
-Oh, come on!
-What's wrong?
Just give me a second.
Gosh!
Yes, hello?
Yeah.
I'm her mother.
Who is this?
Go ahead and open it. It's all right.
Oh my!
ONE MILLION WON
And I need the father's signature here.
Oh, I'm not technically Dong-eun's father.
But I'm like a father to her.
Then,
you sign it.
-Oh.
-Yes.
SETTLEMENT LETTER
Sometimes,
legal matters are important, you know.
I don't have a signature.
Can I just write my name down?
Sure.
You can write your name there,
and rewrite the reason for us.
-Reason?
-It's really short.
"Maladjustment."
ROOM FOR RENT
Did you forget something?
Hey, you didn't know?
Your mom cleared the room out
this morning.
My goodness. This is your school uniform.
I'm sure she will call you.
She's your mom, after all.
Goodness.
SPACE GROUP OF KOREA
ARCHITECTURE AND SOCIETY
REASON FOR WITHDRAWAL: MALADJUSTMENT
GUARDIAN: JEONG MI-HEE
GIMBAP HEAVEN
My scars were itching,
and my stomach was in excruciating pain
from period cramps.
At that moment, I had this thought.
"The pharmacy doesn't open until 9 a.m.,
and the Han River
is just a 20-minute walk away."
"The water will be cold,
and then everything will be okay."
"The scars won't itch anymore."
"What more could I want?"
"This is probably the right thing."
Does Dong-eun
have a pretty face?
From the guys' point of view.
I don't know.
Don't try to act dumb.
Maybe it's not just her face
that's pretty.
Then why didn't you just cover her mouth?
Move. You're heavy.
Where are you going? To get more drinks?
Tell Hye-jeong to go.
I would if it were for drinks.
It's the morning prayer service.
Damn. The geezer will get rid of my studio
if I don't come right away. Fuck!
It's a special service for seniors.
I had to stop him from calling you guys.
Hey. Do you want him to stop calling you?
How many white shirts do you have?
-Amen!
Jesus Christ said,
"If anyone slaps you on the right cheek,
turn to them the other cheek also."
-Amen!
"And if anyone wants to take your shirt,
hand over your coat as well."
-Amen!
"If anyone forces you to go one mile,
go with them two miles--"
-Amen!
-We believe in you, Lord.
-Amen.
Sa-ra's dad's voice cracking
was hilarious.
You should have seen his face!
Maybe he was shocked
that there's nothing to see?
Hey!
-I want chocolate milk.
-Huh?
Okay.
-What about you guys?
-Hye-jeong!
I told you, I'm fasting this week!
Ugh, damn it.
Hey, Gyeong-ran.
How long you gonna cry for? All night?
Stop weeping, you fucking bitch.
Fuck, you're so loud. Damn it.
Gyeong-ran.
Scream again,
and I'll shove this in your mouth.
What is she doing here?
She must be nuts. She came here by choice?
Wow, Dong-eun.
I missed you so much.
You dropped out without even a word.
Your dream that you wrote
on your Cyworld page.
"A wise mother and a kind wife."
Did you mean it?
Really? Did you really write that?
Where the hell is this coming from?
Sa-ra wants to paint.
Jae-jun will inherit a golf course.
Hye-jeong, a flight attendant.
Is your dream
to be a wise mother and a kind wife?
What the fuck?
Why did you leave me out?
I have a dream too.
I'm going to be a millionaire.
I don't have a dream, Dong-eun.
Dreams are for people like you.
You, him, and her.
I pay you to work for me,
after your dreams come true.
I don't need a dream. I need a job.
A job that's not too shabby, you know?
Then I'll probably get married
when I'm young and pretty.
Pick out an eligible bachelor,
and have one or two kids.
Then I'll live happily ever after.
There isn't a word
that summarizes all of that, right?
Yeah, there is.
"Bullshit."
Shut the fuck up, Sa-ra.
So scary!
So?
What's your dream?
You.
Starting today, my dream is you.
I really hope…
we'll see each other again.
SUMMER OF 2006
Quit the monkey business. Put it away!
Hey, don't be too hard on her!
She has so many cigarette burn scars
on her arms and legs.
Do your job.
GED EXAM RESULTS
MOON DONG-EUN
YOU HAVE PASSED THE GED EXAM
FALL OF 2006
2005 SCHOOL YEAR
MATH SECTION
2006 SCHOOL YEAR
SCHOLASTIC ABILITY TEST
FALL OF 2007
FALL OF 2008
Excuse me.
I'm not trying to distract you.
I'm 20 years old,
and my name is Koo Seong-hee.
I heard you're leaving the factory
at the end of this month.
So I just wanted to strike up
a conversation with you before you quit.
Same here. Thank you.
For what?
Walking on your tiptoes.
You saw that?
Anyway, congratulations!
I heard that you got into college.
Wow, you must be so happy.
You can go on group dates
and get a boyfriend in college!
That's not really what I'm looking for.
I'm going to college
'cause there's somewhere
I really need to go.
Where do you need to go?
Samsung?
Hyundai?
I wasn't joking, Yeon-jin.
Ever since that day,
my only dream has always been you.
SUNGWU TEXTILE
SPRING OF 2009
I'll have the strongest coffee
that you have, please. Cold.
I'm quite sleepy.
Would you like an iced Americano
with an extra shot?
Sure. I'll have that.
It will be served at the pickup area.
Next customer, please.
One iced Americano
and one warm mocha latte, please.
I want a ton of whipped cream
and chocolate drizzle on the latte.
We'll be paying separately,
but please put both stamps on my coupon.
I knew you'd say that,
so I didn't bring my wallet.
-Dammit.
-Drinks will be served at the pickup area.
Next customer, please.
Gather a mountain to make some dust,
you know.
Yeo-jeong.
-Gather coupons to make you rich.
-How does that happen?
Help a little brother.
You always say that and make me pay.
Please act like my senior.
Okay.
At least you can get rich
with the coupons.
Coupons can't make me rich.
How is that possible?
WELCOME, FRESHMEN OF 2009!
EUICHEON UNIVERSITY OF EDUCATION
Welcome!
I thought about it every day, Yeon-jin.
Where should I reunite with you?
You have it all.
You are scared of no one.
So, where is the place
that will make you scared,
even for a second?
I couldn't think of any other place.
My own gymnasium of 60 square meters.
HA YE-SOL
Wow, that's just like a fairy tale.
Now I'm going to wield
a very soft, very bright curling iron.
The one that you cherish the most,
Yeon-jin.
Is my story like a fairy tale?
Yes, but I don't like it
because my mom's not the main character.
What makes you think that?
Because my mom is rich.
And the main characters are all poor.
No, you're wrong.
In this story,
your mother is the main character.
Because this story isn't a fairy tale.
It's a fable.
Fog is considered dense
when it has a visibility range
of less than one kilometer.
A fog warning was issued yesterday,
and it is still in effect today.
Did you know
that the main hindrance to safe flights
is not typhoons or lightning, but fog?
"Anyone who injures their neighbor
is to be injured in the same manner."
Although the number of accidents
is the highest on clear days,
the fatality rate
is the highest on foggy days.
Please be careful of the fog.
This is Park Yeon-jin.
"Eye for eye,
tooth for tooth…
…fracture for fracture."
"The one who inflicted the injury
must suffer the same."
I don't know.
That sounds...
too fair to me.